Sevket Yilmaz

Email Address: sevket.yilmaz@outlook.com

Cell: +90-507 205 77 09 Linkedin: <u>sevket-yilmaz</u>

Objective

I am a software engineer with 7+ years of experience and looking forward to joining a progressive organization. I am goal-oriented, self-motivated and committed to the successful outcome of the project. I am willing to work hard and have a great desire to learn.

Skills

OOP, Software Architectures, Design Patterns, C# .NET Framework, .NET Core, Web Services, VB.NET, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, SQL, T-SQL, SOAP, Elasticsearch, MongoDB, Git, TFS, Jira, Agile, Scrum, RabbitMQ, Azure Cloud, Azure DevOps, Docker, Kubernetes

Experience

Kodiks

Software Engineer (01.2020 - ...)

C#, .NET Core, DDD, SaaS, Azure, Docker, Kubernetes, DevOps

- Managed a SaaS platform development team
- Performed requirements analysis, design, development and test management
- Delivered new features in both Agile and SDLC life-cycles
- Created infrastructure with Azure Cloud services and CI/CD pipelines

Arvato - Supply Chain Solutions

Software Engineer (08.2018 - 12.2019)

C#, .NET Core, Web Services, Software Integrations, WMS, B2B, E-Commerce

- Integration with more than 20 e-commerce and ERP software systems
- Maintaining and updating integrations with third-party software
- Developed scheduling OS tasks, web services and reporting-monitoring tools

Bexfa Technology & Software Solutions

Software Engineer (05.2016 - 08.2018)

C#, VB.NET, .NET Framework, Framework Development, ERP, B2B, E-Commerce

- Work as a full-stack developer on an ERP solution
- Worked on company's own (DB & Web) framework
- Design and develop B2B E-Commerce platform for pharmacists

Kobiz Technology R&D

Software Engineer (05.2015 - 05.2016)

JAVA, JSF, JPA, Android, M2M

- Interdisciplinary work and R&D
- Develop a laboratory management software
- Machine to machine communication

Nilaccra Information Technologies

Software Developer (08.2014 - 05.2015)

C#, .NET Framework, CRM, E-Commerce

- Worked as a junior developer with a software team
- Develop features, bug-fixing on an e-commerce website

Education

Technology Faculty, Bachelor's Degree - Firat University

Software Engineering